http://www.njys.org/privacy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar
Fall Online
Privacy Policy for Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts
At Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts, accessible from https://whartonarts.org/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at info@whartonarts.org.
Log Files
Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this as a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Privacy Policies
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts’ Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Wharton Institute for the Performing Arts. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Primary SidebarSearch this website
Recent Posts
Wharton Arts Hosts Virtual Winter Celebration December 18-20
Wharton Institute For The Performing Arts Hosts Virtual Winter Celebration
A Look Inside the Friday Webinars at Wharton Arts
A Look Inside the Monday Master Class Series
In the Media: Live Music Performed at Centennial Park Sunday by NJ Youth Symphony
SUBSCRIBE
TO OUR NEWSLETTER
Top Footer Widget
Select Your Interest:
Performing Arts School
